

SWANN MARTIN

CONTACT INFO

- Brussels
- +32 456 59 60 82
- <u>swannmartin1988@gmail.com</u>
- Portfolio: swannmartin.xyz
- @swann.martin
- https://github.com/swann-martin
- Driving Licence & car
- # Fluent in English, French Native

PROFILE

Web and mobile developer specialised in React and React Native with TypeScript. I worked on several apps for construction industry sector, aerospace, small companies and city councils. I have strong adaptation skills and I am organised. In the past, have worked for years in an English speaking context and lived for 2 years in England.

PROJETS https://github.com/swann-martin

Burger Shop:

React, TypeScript, Supabase

WashatHome

React, Redux, axios, Leaflet, postgres, scss, node My Sofas :

React, Typescript, tailwind-css, vite

Portfolio:

React, TypeScript, Scss

NewsApp:

Flutter & api News

Jummp a CV Generator:

Symfony, PHP, twig, jQuery, CSS

HOBBIES



Climbing sports



GNU/Linux,



Decentralization



Open Source



House Renovation

REACT DEVELOPER

SKILLS

Advanced

React &







Tailwindess

Intermediate

Expo

React Native

Jass

Zustand



Back-end

(s) Node

postgres|mySQL firebase



Other







Organised, Rigourous, Flexible, Reactive, Curious Can do attitude, Decisive

EXPERIENCE



FREELANCE DEVELOPER

Freelance Developer | February 2023

Freelance developer, specialized in React, React Native with Typescript. See my profile on Malt.be



[</>] DEVELOPER

Beecoming | December 2021 - November 2022 As a developper there, I was in charge of implementing new features, fixing bugs, and turning designs into code. I mainly coded in React Native.

- Technologies used: React-Native, ReactJS, Angular, Ionic, Vue, SCSS, Websockets, PrestaShop, Node
- Langages: TypeScript/JavaScript, Php, .Net
- Tools: Agile, Scrum, Git, Jira, Office 360, ios, android



SALES REPRESENTATIVE LANGUAGE COURSE Oxford Intensive School of English | 2014 - 2020

- Managing a booking office in Bordeaux & Lille
- Bookings Average Annual Income 250 000€
- Organized, work in English and French, management

FORMATION

O'CLOCK: BACHELOR EQUIVALENT

Training React.JS | June 2021 - Aug 2021

Training in React.js, Redux.

End of training project: Technologies: React, Redux, Node, postgreSql

WEBFORCE 3 BORDEAUX

Certification Dev Web | Jan 2021 - April 2021

Certifications professionnelles CNCP (catégorie C):

• Techniques d'intégration Web (front-end) : (HTML / CSS,

JavaScript / jQuery, Angular, CMS: Wordpress)

• <u>Techniques de développement Web (back-end) :</u> (MySQL, PHP, Symfony).

End of training project: CV generator website. Technologies: Symfony/Twig/SQL/CSS

UNIVERSITY OF PORTSMOUTH / PARIS X Master2 FLE / PGCE MFL | Sept 2011 - Juin 2013

- Double diploma Master 2 Teaching Modern Foreign Languages | FLE

LYCÉE MIREILLE GRENET COMPIEGNE

BACCALAUREAT Sciences Engineering technologies spe Electronics with Honors | 2007